

Morenike Oyewole

I'm a knowledgeable Frontend developer adept for creating user-friendly websites that meets clients need. I'am also an experienced Pianist and music teacher with vast experience in the music industry. I'm from Oyo state and I am currently based in Lagos, Nigeria.

Hobbies/Interests:

Surfing, online shopping, coding, playing piano, teaching



Professional Skills HTML CSS Javascript JQuery React Web design Soft Skills Effective communication Team work Time management Interpersonal skills Fast learner Attention to details

Work Experience

Manifield Manpower Consultancy / Assistant Technical Officer

Mar, 2021 - PRESENT. Lagos, Nigeria

- Cooperated with the senior Chief technology officer to align management of junior staff with business priorities and goals.
- Performed hands-on work (building and developing) on

Freelancer / Pianist

Jan, 2016 - PRESENT. Lagos, Nigeria

- Formed and played piano for an All Female band (Bandittude).
- Performed with several artists including Rudeboy, Eva, Muna, Yinka Davis at different functions in and out of the country.

- technologies such as wordpress, Podio and click-up
- Served as Information Technology (IT) advisor to HRs
- Coordinated with management teams to plan, develop, align and execute strategies that would meet client's vision, mission and purpose.

HOME Music School / Music Teacher

Jan, 2015- PRESENT. Lagos, Nigeria

- Taught private music lessons to students including (special needs).
- Prepared students for live performances and ABRSM (UK) practical and theory exams.
- Developed strong working relationships with teachers, parents and students to propel school and departmental vision and goals.

Trainee / Front-end developer

Jun, 2020 - PRESENT, Lagos, Nigeria

- Maintain and improve website.
- Develop user-friendly and responsive web pages using markup languages like HTML, CSS and Javascript

Education and Couses

Yaba College Of Technology / National Diploma

Musical Society Of Nigeria (MUSON) / Grade V Music Theory

Sep, 2012 - Feb, 2015, Yaba, Nov,2015 - Nov, 2016, Lagos, Lagos Nigeria Nigeria Associated Board of the Royal Schools of Music (ABRSM UK) / Grade V Piano

Jul 2018- Jul, 2019, Lagos, Nigeria

Front-end Respons
development course Design - Udemy Freecode

Responsive Web Design -Freecodecamp

Jul 2020 - Sept, 2020

Feb 2021 - Present

Becoming a better Music teacher - Futurelearn Mar 2021 -

Present

Contact Me

\(+2348099772916

